initiating git repository and why
    
man nutzt git init um ein git repository für den aktuellen
ordner zu erstellen. Dadurch kann man dann die Files tracken
allerdings muss man dies erst noch git dann manually "sagen
also mit git add <file> kann man dann die untracked files
zum tracker hinzufügen und dann werden sie nicht als untracked
angezeigt, wenn man git status nutzt. Dann werden einerseits
die veränderungen seit dem letzten commit angezeigt, aber auch
die getrackten und ungetrackten files in der directory. und
ebenfalls die gesamtzahl der commits.

difference of staging area to repository and working dir
  
die staging area ist der workspace, zu dem man files hinzufügen kann
daher kann man in einer working directory mehrere files, die von
nacheinander ausgestellten commits getrackt werden, haben. 
Das bedeutet man kann files erst später hinzufügen aber danach nicht
wieder löschen. Die Staging area wird auch erzeugt und nachdem man
commited hat, wird die staging area wieder gelöscht. Sie ist also
im gegensatz zum repository und zur working directory nur temporär.

How can you use the staging area to make sure you have one commit per logical change?
  
Wenn man files bearbeitet, dann kann man sobald man den logischen Schritt fertig
hat mit git diff die changes noch einmal nachverfolgen/korrigieren. Dann kann man
wenn man die File dann gestaged hat, diese mit dem vorherigen commit vergleichen
und nochmals die changes untersuchen. Wenn man sich dann sicher ist, dass alles
richtig ist, kann man das dann commiten. Ebenfalls kann man schauen ob es schon
eine Änderung gab, da man ja die Files mit Änderung in der Staging area ablegen 
sollte. Und wenn man differenzen in mehreren Files hat, dann kann man relativ 
einfach diese hinzufügen und adden. Ein bisschen wie eine vorsortierung, bevor
man etwas verkauft. "Ich will den den den, ach nein den noch nicht. Fertig bitte 
zur kasse." oder wie der Einkaufswagen bei Amazon.

What are some situations when branches would be helpful in keeping your history organized? How would branches help?
 
when having different versions of a code, which include seperate features,
like different languages, maybe a different feature like an easier mode,
or trying out something new like an ipad version. Then branches
help to keep the things organized, because they have names, which
in the best case describe the differences. The branches allow one
to work on the different features and later merge them into one
program again, once the new feature or so is necessary or useful
to incorporate into the main program.
  

How do the diagrams help you visualize the branch structure?
 
the diagrams help to understand the structure of all the
branches. Where they part from master, which commits the
parental commits are and which commit should be turned
into a branch to reach them. also when there are a lot of
branches its hard to keep track of them. so having a branch
diagram helps to remember all the branch names and their
structure.

What is the result of merging two branches together? Why do we represent it in the diagram the way we do?
 
When merging two branches, the result is a new commit, which
incorporates the changes from both branches. The branch, which
is checked out is taken as the branch for the new commit and the
commit is has two parent commits - one from each merged branch.
Therefore the presentation in the diagram is correct, by show
two arrows to each of the old branch tips. The two old branches
with all of their commits can be accesed through git log, but
they might intertwine, because they are sorted by the time stamps 
of the commit. when not having a linear commit history, the 
changes in a commit compared to its parent commit can be shown
with git show <commit-id> . Therefore the id of the parent doesn´t
have to be copied and pasted.
What are the pros and cons of Git’s automatic merging vs. always doing merges manually?
 
Merges, especially when they are big, so change a lot of code, 
are quite work intensive to do manually. Especially when having
large programs keeping track is hard. When merging automatic
though, is not always perfect, but thanks to git, the issues
which occur, are told to the user and they can resolve them 
manually, so most of the tricky work is done by the program
and there is not that much space for error anymore.
